The Sawyers live at 87 King Street.
Sawyers一家住在国王街87号.
In the morning,
早上,
Mr. Sawyer goes to work and the children go to school.
Sawyers先生去上班, 孩子们去上学.
Their father takes them to school every day.
父亲每天送孩子们去上学.
Mrs. Sawyer stays at home every day.
Sawyers夫人每天呆在家里.
She does the housework.
她料理家务.
She always eats her lunch at noon.
她总是在正午吃午饭.
In the afternoon, she usually sees her friends.
下午, 她通常会见她的朋友们.
They often drink tea together.
她们经常在一起喝茶.
In the evening,
傍晚,
the children come home from school.
孩子们放学回家.
They arrive home early.
他们到家很早.
Mr. Sawyer comes home from work.
Sawyers先生下班回家.
He arrives home late.
他到家很晚.
At night, the children always do their homework.
晚上, 孩子们总是做他们的作业.
Then they go to bed.
然后去睡觉.
Mr. Sawyer usually reads his newspaper,
Sawyers先生总是读报纸,
but sometimes he and his wife watch television.
但有时和他的妻子一起看电视.